downscripts.com 2017-11-30

# DownScripts Privacy Policy

This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

**Note:**  the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

**VISTOR STATS**

We are using two different web analytics services to improve and optimize our website.  
Both services use cookies to track visitor behaviour. For further details please visit their privacy policies. 

  1. [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics/) ([Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy.html))

**AD NETWORKS**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies 

We use the following ad networks:

  * Google Adsense ([Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy.html))

**ESPECIALLY GOOGLE ADSENSE PRIVACY POLICY**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**DISTRIBUTION OF INFORMATION**

We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.

**PRIVACY CONTACT INFORMATION**

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below: 

By e-mail: contact us.

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy without notice. 

2004 - 2013 DownScripts. All rights reserved.
